Finding Aid for the John J. Bonica Papers Biomed.0118
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Conferences and Travel
  - International Cancer Congress (14th: 21 Aug 1986 - 27 Aug 1986: Budapest, Hungary). (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council (05 Oct 1986 - 11 Oct 1986: Stockholm, Sweden). (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (17 Oct 1986 - 21 Oct 1986: Las Vegas, NV). (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Pacific Coast Society of Orthodontists, Hospital Celebration, (26 Oct 1986 - 30 Oct 1986: Los Angeles, CA; Mexico City, Mexico). (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - International Conference on Neurogenic and Myofascial Pain, (03 Nov 1986 - 09 Nov 1986: Valley Stream, NY; Washington, DC). (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Pharmacia National Sales Meeting (11 Jan 1987 - 12 Jan 1987: Corpus Christi, TX). (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - John J. Bonica Visiting Professorship (06 Apr 1987 - 10 Apr 1987: Seattle, WA). (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Vacation, Lecture, IASP Meeting (12 Apr 1987 - 05 May 1987: Honolulu, HI; Los Angeles, CA). (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - John J. Bonica Award and Lecture, 9th [Howard L. Fields]; (19 May 1987 - 23 May 1987: New York, NY; Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada). (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - World Congress on Pain, 5th, and Sattelite Symposium on (26 Jul 1987 - 07 Aug 1987: Venice, Italy; Hamburg, West Germany). (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - International Meeting on Recent Progress in Oncology; (04 Sep 1987 - 23 Sep 1987: Sardinia, Modena; Italy). (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - American Society of Anesthesiology. Meeting (10 Oct 1987 - 14 Oct 1987: Atlanta, GA). (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - International Conference on Neuropathic and Musculoskeletal (2nd: 04 Nov 1987 - 06 Nov 1987: Valley Stream, NY). (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Advances in Pain Management (6th: 14 Nov 1987 - 15 Nov 1987: New York, NY). (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - The Importance and Magnitude of Cancer Pain (01 Dec 1987 - 02 Dec 1987: New York, NY). (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Alpha Omega Achievement Medal (27 Dec 1987 - 29 Dec 1987: Seattle, WA). (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - University of Miami Pain Center (20 Jan 1988 - 22 Jan 1988: Miami Beach, FL). (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - The Year in Internal Medicine (28 Jan 1988 - 29 Jan 1988: Chicago, IL). (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Obstetric/Anesthesia Conference (16th: 07 Feb 1988 - 11 Feb 1988: Waikiki, Hawaii). (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Advances in Epidemiology of Pain. Workshop (23 Feb 1988 - 26 Feb 1988: San Diego, CA). (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Vacation (07 Mar 1988 - 16 Apr 1988: Honolulu, HI). (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Meeting & (13th: 17 Mar 1988 - 20 Mar 1988: San Francisco, CA). (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Bristol-Myers Press Conference (20 Apr 1988 - 21 Apr 1988: New York, NY). (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Pharmacia Deltec Dedication (25 Apr 1988: Minneapolis, MN). (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - World Congress of Anaesthesiologists (22 May 1988 - 28 May 1988: Washington, DC). (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - International Symposium Regional Anesthesia (2nd: 28 May 1988 - 30 May 1988: Williamsburg, VA). (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - International Pain Foundation. Board Meeting (02 Jun 1988 - 05 Jun 1988: Los Angeles, CA). (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - International Congress on Cancer Pain (2nd: 14 Jun 1988 - 17 Jun 1988: Rye, NY). (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Bristol-Myers Pain Award (21 Jun 1988 - 22 Jun 1988: New York, NY). (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - International Symposium on Pediatric Pain (1st: 22 Jul 1988 - 24 Jul 1988: Seattle, WA). (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - International Postgraduate Practical Course on Pain Therapy (4th: 04 Sep 1988 - 09 Sep 1988: Vicenza, Italy). (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (08 Oct 1988 - 12 Oct 1988: San Francisco, CA). (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - International Conference on Neuropathic and Musculoskeletal (3rd: 18 Oct 1988 - 21 Oct 1988: Uniondale, NY). (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Japan Society of Clinical Anesthesia. Meeting (8th: 10 Nov 1988 - 12 Nov 1988: Miyazaki City, Japan). (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - University of Iowa Visiting Professorship; Pain Management (07 Dec 1988 - 09 Dec 1988: Iowa City, IA; Brooklyn, NY). (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Meeting (16 Feb 1989 - 19 Feb 1989: Key West, FL). (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Obstetric/Anesthesia Conference (17th: 27 Feb 1989 - 02 Mar 1989: Waikiki, Hawaii). (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Meeting (14th: 31 Mar 1989 - 02 Apr 1989: Boston, MA). (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Marquette University Alumni Merit Award (08 Apr 1989: Milwaukee, WI). (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - John J. Bonica Visiting Professorship (14 Apr 1989: Seattle, WA). (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - John J. Bonica Award and Lecture, 11th [William D. Willis]; (08 May 1989 - 05 Jun 1989: New York, NY; Lisbon, Portugal; Oslo, Norway). (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Pain Award Selection Committee Meeting (11 May 1989 - 13 May 1989: New York, NY). (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Sons of Italy (10 Jun 1989: Seattle, WA). (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Humanitarian of the Year Award in Anesthesiology (15 Jun 1989 - 16 Jun 1989: Columbus, OH). (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Northwestern University. Commencement (17 Jun 1989: Evanston, IL). (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Peter Winter Chairmanship of Ten Years (24 Jun 1989: Pittsburgh, PA). (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Pain & Cancer: Innovations in Pain Control (05 Aug 1989 - 06 Aug 1989: Pittsburgh, PA). (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Vacation (28 Aug 1989 - 09 Oct 1989: Milan, Rome, Calvi, Filicudi; Italy). (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (13 Oct 1989 - 17 Oct 1989: New Orleans, LA). (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - American Pain Society/ International Pain Foundation (25 Oct 1989 - 30 Oct 1989: Phoenix, AZ). (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Lea & Febiger (11 Feb 1990 - 12 Feb 1990: Philadelphia, PA). (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Meeting (25 Mar 1990 - 27 Mar 1990: Orlando, FL). (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Association of University Anesthetists. Meeting (37th: 03 May 1990 - 05 May 1990: Seattle, WA). (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - John J. Bonica Award and Lecture [Ada G. Rogers] (12th: 14 May 1990: New York, NY). (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - St. Luke's-Roosevelt Hospital Center Pain Management (15 May 1990 - 16 May 1990: New York, NY). (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Bristol-Myers Squibb Pain Award Selection Committee (16 May 1990 - 18 May 1990: New York, NY). (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Animal Pain and Its Control (25 Jun 1990 - 28 Jun 1990: Ithaca, NY). (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Bristol-Myers Squibb Symposium on Pain Research. Pain and (1st: 12 Jul 1990 - 14 Jul 1990: Ann Arbor, MI). (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Pharmacia (06 Aug 1990: Minneapolis, MN). (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - European Congress of Anaesthesiology (8th: 09 Sep 1990 - 15 Sep 1990: Warsaw, Poland). (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (18 Oct 1990 - 23 Oct 1990: Las Vegas, NV). (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - American Pain Society. Scientific Meeting (9th: 24 Oct 1990 - 27 Oct 1990: St. Louis, MO). (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - International Symposium. The Pain Clinic (4th: 18 Nov 1990 - 21 Nov 1990: Kyoto, Japan). (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Pharmacia Deltec (22 Jan 1991 - 23 Jan 1991: St. Paul, MN). (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Postgraduate Course in Anesthesiology (36th: 22 Feb 1991 - 26 Feb 1991: Snowbird, UT). (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Obstetric/Anesthesia Conference (19th: 28 Mar 1991 - 29 Mar 1991: Honolulu, HI). (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Meeting (16th: 04 Apr 1991 - 07 Apr 1991: Cincinnati, OH). (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Landacre Day (11 Apr 1991: Columbus, OH). (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - John J. Bonica Award and Lecture, 13th [B. Berthold Wolff]; (15 Apr 1991 - 21 Apr 1991: New York, NY). (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - John J. Bonica Visiting Professorship (07 May 1991 - 11 May 1991: Seattle, WA). (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Bristol-Myers Squibb Symposium on Pain Research. (2nd: 20 May 1991 - 22 May 1991: Galveston, TX). (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Zentraleuropäischer Anästhesiekongress (09 Sep 1991 - 14 Sep 1991: Interlaken, Switzerland). (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - International Association for the Study of Pain. Council (01 Oct 1991 - 02 Oct 1991: Toledo, Spain). (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (26 Oct 1991 - 30 Oct 1991: San Francisco, CA). (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - American Pain Society. Scientific Meeting (10th: 07 Nov 1991 - 10 Nov 1991: New Orleans, LA). (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Anesthesia and Critical Care Conference (06 Dec 1991 - 08 Dec 1991: Chicago, IL). (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - PGA (07 Dec 1991 - 14 Dec 1991: New York, NY). (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Pharmacia Deltec (20 Jan 1992: St. Paul, MN). (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - The John J. Bonica Hawaii Pain Conference (23 Mar 1992 - 27 Mar 1992: Maui, HI). (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - American Socity of Regional Anesthesia. Meeting (17th: 26 Mar 1992 - 29 Mar 1992: Tampa, FL). (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - John J. Bonica Visiting Professorship (24 Apr 1992: Seattle, WA). (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Cancer Pain Management: A Practical Approach (02 May 1992: Columbus, OH). (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - John J. Bonica Award and Lecture [Ulf Lindblom] (14th: 03 May 1992 - 09 May 1992: New York, NY). (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Marquette University. Class of 1942. Fifty Year Reunion (15 May 1992 - 18 May 1992: Milwaukee, WI). (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Tauber (24 May 1992 - 25 May 1992: San Francisco, CA). (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - International Symposium on Advances in Pain Management (28 May 1992 - 31 May 1992: Cleveland, OH). (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - International Conference and Workshops on Neuropathic, (03 Jun 1992 - 06 Jun 1992: Sheraton, NY). (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Joint ESRA/ASRA Congress, 3rd; ESRA Congress, 11th (09 Jun 1992 - 12 Jun 1992: Brussels, Belgium). (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - World Congress of Anaesthesiologists (10th: 12 Jun 1992 - 19 Jun 1992: The Hague, Netherlands). (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Bristol-Myers Squibb Symposium on Pain Research (3rd: 23 Jul 1992 - 26 Jul 1992: Seattle, WA). (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Wood Library-Museum Building Dedication (15 Aug 1992: Park Ridge, IL). (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - IASP Council Meeting (02 Sep 1992 - 07 Sep 1992: Budapest, Hungary). (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - American Pain Society. Meeting (22 Oct 1992 - 25 Oct 1992: San Diego, CA). (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - John J. Bonica Hawaii Pain Conference (2nd: 30 Mar 1993 - 02 Apr 1993: Wailea, HI). (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - John J. Bonica Lecture (15th: 15 Apr 1993: Seattle, WA). (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - ASRA Meeting (06 May 1993: Indian Wells, CA). (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - John J. Bonica Distinguished Lecturer (13 May 1993 - 16 May 1993: Seattle, WA). (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Reception for Thomas F. Hornbein (17 Jun 1993: Seattle, WA). (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - World Congress on Pain (7th: 22 Aug 1993 - 27 Aug 1993: Paris, France). (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Cancer Pain Management: Defining New Standards of Care (28 Oct 1993: Seattle, WA). (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Current Concepts in Acute, Chronic, and Cancer Pain (08 Dec 1993 - 10 Dec 1993: New York, NY). (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - John J. Bonica Obstetric/Anesthesia Conference, 22nd; John (02 Apr 1994 - 07 Apr 1994: Honolulu, Maui; HI). (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - American Society of Regional Anesthesia. Meeting (19th: 07 Apr 1994 - 10 Apr 1994: Chicago, IL). (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - International Congess Pain Clinic (6th: 15 Apr 1994 - 20 Apr 1994: Atlanta, GA). (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - California Society of Anesthesiologists. Meeting (19 May 1994 - 22 May 1994: Monterey, CA). (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Bristol-Myers Squibb Symposium on Pain (5th: 23 May 1994 - 25 May 1994: Iowa City, IO). (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, 1983-1987 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, 1983 and Jan - Aug,1984 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, Sep - Nov, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, Jan - Apr, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, May - Jun, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, Jul - Oct, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Invitations Unable to Accept, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 55)
- Administrative
  - Tacoma General Hospital
    - Equipment and property file, nd. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Equipment and property file, 1959. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Equipment Committee, 1962. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - List of contents [of] boxes in storage, nd. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Photography Equipment, 1959. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Bennett Ventilator Equipment, 1964. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Bird Equipment, 1960. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Anesthesia Equipment Instructions, nd. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - TGH Equipment, nd. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - [Equipment brochures], 1961. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Dermometer, nd. (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Dermalor, 1956. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Cardioscope, 1955. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Oscillocardiograph, 1955. (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Medical Films, nd. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Medical Films, 1960. (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Medical Motion Pictures, nd. (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Books--Inventory and Orders, 1962. (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Boobs [sic]--Catalogs, 1961-1962. (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Book Inventory and Reprint List, 1960. (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Anesthesia Records--Samples, 1962. (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Cortisone-Like Preparations, nd. (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Medicolegal, 1957. (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Welfare, 1956. (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Medicare, 1958. (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Change-Over Battle, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - T.G.H. Disaster Plan, nd. (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Exch. Vis. Prog. P-519, nd. (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Public Relations, nd. (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Publicity, nd. (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - TGH Anesthesiology Department, nd. (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Announcement Cards, 1957. (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Hospital Planning, nd. (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - School of Anesthesia, 1948. (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Survey of Anesthesiology, 1956-1958. (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Minerva Anesthesiological, 1955. (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Journal of Anesthesiology, 1958-1959. (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Journal of the American Medical Association, 1957-1958. (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Clin Pharm and Therap., 1959. (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Current Medical Digest, 1959-1960. (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - The Far East Journal of Anesthesia, 1956-1957. (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Resenha--(Brazilian Journal), 1959. (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - TGH Med. Staff--General, 1963. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - TGH Recovery Room, 1960. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Dr. A. O'Keefe--Correspondence, 1967. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, Margaret, 1962. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Post graduate courses--refresher courses, 1962. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - State Department Forms, nd. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - GP. INS. blank forms, nd. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Record of Lectures, 1960-1961. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Teaching Prog, 1959-1960. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - University teaching program, 1964. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Lecture Sched., 1955-1959. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Abbott--What's New, 1960. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Proposed Writings, 1956-1959. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Renal Function Test, 1961. (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Book Reviews by JJB, 1961. (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Abstracts, 1957. (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Bylaws, rules and regulations TGH, nd. (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Changes of Status, 1956. (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Visitors to Department, 1961. (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - TGH School of Nursing, 1962. (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Survey--Neonatal Deaths, 1936-1954. (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - [Drug literature], nd. (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Narcotics, nd. (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - "U" Call schedule, 1962. (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Bonica--Handwritten Notes, 1960?. (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Tacoma Resident Lectures (a), 1960. (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Tacoma Resident Lectures (b), 1960?. (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Residency Information, 1965. (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Staff and resident duties, nd. (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - University of Washington resident application forms, nd. (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Resident evaluation forms, nd. (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Application forms, nd. (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - University applications for residency, 1962. (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - A.B.A. TGH Residency, nd. (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Residents' Papers, nd. (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Teaching Program, nd. (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - ABA res. TGH, 1961. (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Outside Training Program, nd. (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Applications Closed, 1957-8-9. (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Applications Closed, 1960-1961. (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Res. Exams, Dec., 1961. (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Anderson, Charles, 1960. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Arduin, Gilberto, nd. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Baird, Robert A., 1961. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Bean, Glenn M., nd. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Bigornia, Generoso, nd. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Brawand, Kurt, 1959. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Brena, Stefano, 1956-1957. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Chamblee, WM C., 1959-1961. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Chapman, Kyile, nd. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Dahl, Arne, nd. (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Danford, Henry W., 1960-1962. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Dixon, H. Loring, 1962. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Dreher, Charles, nd. (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Esdale, Willian, nd. (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Esquivel, Raymundo, 1960. (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Eylander, Edward, nd. (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Fisher, Robert, 1952. (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Flynn, William E., 1963. (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Fortuna, Armando, 1958. (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Gale, D. Anthony, nd. (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Gherardi, Armando, 1951. (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Glaser, Charles E., 1958-1960. (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Glenn, David, 1969. (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Guilfoil, Erna, 1967. (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Hadfield, Dale, nd. (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Hill, Jesse, nd. (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Hofmeister, Ilse, 1952. (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Hori, Kiyoaky, nd. (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Lawrence, Vans, nd. (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Maher, William D., nd. (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Mandelstam, J., nd. (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Manasan, Milagros, 1961. (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Mason, Dr. Gene, nd. (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Matzinger, Philip, nd. (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - McQuarrie, L., nd. (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Mena, Carlos, nd. (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Minelli, Juan E., nd. (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Morley, Leonard, nd. (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Monk, Benj F., nd. (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Molina, Fausto J., 1957. (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Mix, George, 1952. (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Morrow, Gay, nd. (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Dr. Vincent Murphy, nd. (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Dr. Wm. McKinley, nd. (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Dr. N. B. Nishimura, nd. (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Dr. A. J. O'Keefe, nd. (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Dr. Lilia Peneyhra, nd. (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Dr. J. M. G. Ritchie, 1958. (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Dr. R.R. Sackman, nd. (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Dr. K. N. Scott, nd. (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Dr. pacita Siapno, nd. (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Sherry, Dr. R. A., nd. (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Stern, Dr. Ernest, nd. (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Stovall, Dr. R. M., 1960-1961. (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Rorres-Reyes E., nd. (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - Walker, Murray K., nd. (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Weis, Donald R., nd. (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - Maurice Yoachim, nd. (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Thomas Q. Ziegler, 1958-1960. (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - Drs. Luis and Maria Moreno, 1959. (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Kenzo Kaneko, M.D., 1961. (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Arturo S. Opaso, M.D., 1961. (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - Rizzi, Ruggero, M.D., 1960. (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - Seely, Howard C., 1960. (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - Sobel, Otylia, M.D., nd. (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - Arthur J. Sugiyhama, M.D., 1961. (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - Hideaki Ueyama, M.D., 1960. (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - John W. Wallace M.D., 1961. (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - Wilson, Arthur N. Jr., M.D., 1960. (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS. Open heart surgery. Patient data, 1961-1962. (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS. Patient mortality, 1957-1961. (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS. Blood loss reports. Patient records, 1950?. (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS. Brachial block anesthesia records, 1946-1948. (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS. Resident exams, 1959. (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS. Surgical anesthesia log book, 1958. (Box 154, Folder unknown container)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS. Anesthesia patient log book, 1947. (Box 154, Folder unknown container)
  - University of Washington
    - Referral Letters to Dr. B, A-C, 72-77. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Referral Letters to Dr. B, D-H, 72-77. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Referral Letters to Dr. B, I-N, 72-77. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Referral Letters to Dr. B, O-Z, 72-77. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Old calendars, 1973-1976. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Calendars, 1977. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Calendars, 1978. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Calendars, 1979. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Letters of Recommendation: D-H, 1974-1981. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Letters of Recommendation: A-C, 1974-1981. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Letters of Recommendation: Q-Z, 1974-1981. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Letters of Recommendation: I-M, 1974-1981. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Lettters of Recommendation: A, nd. (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Letters of Recommendation: B 1/2, nd. (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Letters of Recommendation: B 2/2, nd. (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Letters of Recommendation: C, nd. (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Letters of Recommendation: D, nd. (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Letters of Recommendation: E, F, nd. (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Letters of Recommendation: G, H, nd. (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Letters of Recommendation: I, J, nd. (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Letters of Recommendation: K, L, nd. (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Letters of Recommendation: M, N, nd. (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Letters of Recommendation: O, P, nd. (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Letters of Recommendation: Q, R, nd. (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Letters of Recommendation: S, nd. (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Letters of Recommendation: T, nd. (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Letters of Recommendation: U, V, W, nd. (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Letters of Recommendation: X, Y, Z, nd. (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - U of W Personnel, nd. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Topical anesthesia. Dr. Kennedy, nd. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Report. Pilot study. General Inventory of Cancer Activities., 1964. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Post-graduate course--September, 1963. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Yearly Time Schedule, nd. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Post graduate course in anesthesiology--october, 1961. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - List of approved residencies in anesthesiology JournalA.M.A., nd. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Course Census Report, 1964. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Teaching programs--other departments, nd. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Postgraduate course in anesth., 1962. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Postgraduate courses--evaluation questionaires, nd. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Survey: Nurse anesthetists in university hospitals, nd. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Survey: Obstetrical Anesthesia Training in US, nd. (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Residency program William E. Bageant, M.D. Washington D.C, nd. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Residents' stipends--other dept., nd. (Box 38, Folder 15)